ebolaplay.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy » EBOLAPLAY

E-BOLA MÉDIA Kft. is committed to providing the highest possible standard of protection for personal data and to entirely meeting all prevailing legal obligations.

We take all the measures required to keep you fully informed of the details of data protection governing the use of the Ebola website or any of the services provided by Ebola, furthermore, in the case of information collection, we ensure that data is managed in a secure manner and is protected against damage, we have established and operate the technical systems of data management required for this purpose.

Below you can find general information on what data is collected when content provided via the Ebola Play system is viewed or when the services of Ebola Play are used as a Publisher or when Ebola’s own website is visited, and what purposes such data is used for.

## What is the Ebola Play?

Ebola Play is an ad network operated by E-BOLA Média Kft., which predominantly publishes advertisements and other promotional materials on the basis of assignments of advertisers contracted to our company. Such content is chiefly published on websites that are operated by other companies, the owners or operators of those websites are registered as publishers on the website of Ebola and are members of the ad network of Ebola Play.

## Our Privacy Policy

It is of the utmost importance to note that the scope of information we collect and use and the way in which such data is used may vary depending on what services you use; therefore, our information collection is essentially based on two separate systems, both relying on different principles:

  1. Should you visit any of the websites managed by Ebola or alternatively, view an advertisement or content that is published in the framework of the Ebola Play service, Ebola will not collect any personal data or information from or about you from which you can be identified. In this case, Ebola may exclusively collect non-personally identifiable, anonymous information about the use of the specific website, e.g. relating to the content you view in the framework of Ebola Play (without any direct identification) or the advertisements you click on etc. For detailed information please visit link to the privacy information below.
  2. 2\. Should you wish to use Ebola’s services as a publisher, you must first register on the Ebola Play website and give the basic personal details required there (for further details please read the Privacy Policy). In this case, data you have provided will be used to the extent required by the service to be provided by us and on the basis of your explicit consent. For detailed information please visit link to the privacy policy below.

If you have any questions in connection with the above-mentioned information collection, please contact us any time using the email address [info@ebolaplay.com](mailto:info@ebolaplay.com).

Ebola reserves the right to amend, at any time, unilaterally, its Privacy Policy and Rules, in accordance with the governing law. In the case of such an event, the details of all amendments will be published on our website.

## COLLECTION OF ANONYMOUS INFORMATION IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THE EBOLA PLAY AND THE EBOLA WEBSITE PRIVACY INFORMATION

## What data is collected in relation to the use of the websites and the Ebola Play content located on the websites?

If you do not use Ebola’s other services in the framework of which, based on your voluntary choice, you explicitly give personal data relevant to you, Ebola will not collect or process any personal information on you.

However, upon visiting the websites operated by Ebola (in particular, www.ebolaplay.com, www.ebolamedia.com and vid4u.org), and websites embedding the Ebola Play that are operated by a third party which is a member of the ad network (jointly referred to as **“Websites”** ) and by downloading and viewing the specific content, you give consent to the service provider E-BOLA Média Kft. (registered office: 1026 Budapest, Riadó u. 7.) to collect data and information given in this privacy policy ( **“Privacy Policy”** ) and to locate cookies required for the recording.

Such information includes data from your PC that is generated whilst using the Websites and the services of the Ebola Play, this is automatically recorded by the system of the service provider as an result of technical processes.

Unless you have disabled cookies on your PC, the data which is recorded automatically will be automatically logged at the start up of the specific Ebola Play content and at the time of exiting the Websites.

Such data include:

**Cookies:** cookies are short text files that are placed on the hard disk of the user’s PC by the website and include information about the user. For example, if a user clicks on an advertisement published on a specific publisher website in the framework of the Ebola Play, the website may place a cookie on the user’s PC, which records the specific advertisement as a preference. When the user visits that publisher website at a later time, the content displayed there will be compiled in accordance with the preferences relating to the commercial video which was viewed earlier.

**Web beacons** (also called GIF files, pixels or Internet tags): such data is used by the website to follow up visits on the specific website, so that the service provider can obtain general information about the user’s online surfing.

**Log files:** the internet browser also transfers certain data to the website automatically, such as the IP address of the user’s PC (e.g. 110.256.55.01), the name of the domain from which the user visited the website as well as the subsites visited by the user within the website and also the content viewed on the website. Like all other Internet service providers, Ebola also analyses this data so that it can determine which areas of the publisher websites might be more popular than the others.

**Viewing data of contents distributed via the Ebola Play network.** In order to provide service to the users in an appropriate manner, Ebola analyses the viewing data of the content distributed via Ebola Play, and collects anonymous data relating to the ratings of the specific content through an IT procedure specifically developed for this purpose.

## How is information used?

Data collected using the techniques mentioned above cannot be used to identify the user; neither does Ebola link such data with other data so it can be used for identification.

The primary purpose of the use of such data is to allow Ebola to provide the Ebola Play service in an effective and appropriate manner, this requires the follow-up of ratings relating to the content distributed via the Ebola Play, and screening possible abuses in connection with it. Ebola may also use the data specified in this Privacy Policy, among others, to note your personal preferences (e.g. content viewed mostly via the Ebola Play), accordingly, like other service providers. Ebola may also use such data to form the advertisement related experience according to the user’s demands (as previously stated, this is accomplished without the identification of the user).

In addition to the above, Ebola may use that information to analyse use related tendencies and to accomplish advertising purposes achievable through the service, in particular, to transfer advertisements disseminated in the framework of the Ebola Play to the most appropriate and targeted consumers, to improve and develop the service and the function of the Ebola’ website and also to obtain comprehensive data regarding the traffic on the Websites and the entire use of the Ebola Play service. 

Ebola may use data obtained in this way to make and analyse statistics on the use of the Websites and the Ebola Play and to transfer statistical data that cannot be used for identification (e.g. number of visitors, the most popular topics and content) to a third party, in particular to companies advertising through the Ebola Play. In addition, Ebola may also publish a summary of such anonymous data.

## What options do you have? Disabling Cookies:

If you do not wish Ebola to collect data in relation to the use of the Website or the Ebola Play by you (e.g. in connection with the viewing of specific content), **you can partly or entirely disable the use of cookies** by changing the settings in your Internet browser. It is also possible to modify the settings of the cookie messages in another way. 

In doing so you will accept that advertisements are still displayed on the Websites, however those ads will not be selected according to your preferences. Furthermore, you acknowledge that all those included in this category will be without prejudice towards Ebola’s right to collect anonymous data using an IT procedure developed for this purpose. This data, due to it’s connection to the ratings of specific Ebola Play content, is required in order to allow Ebola to provide it’s services in conformity with it’s contracts.

## Cookies placed by third parties:

The Publisher websites embedding the Ebola Play may include pieces of information, in particular advertisements, that are provided by third parties unrelated to E-BOLA Média Kft. Said third parties may also place cookies or web beacons on the user’s PC or collect data using similar technologies so that they can send advertisement messages to the user in connection with their own services. In these cases, data management is governed by data protection rules of those third parties and E-BOLA Média Kft. assumes no liability in relation to such data management.

## EBOLA PLAY PUBLISHERS’ PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy ( **“Privacy Policy”** ) applies exclusively to those who have registered as publishers ( **“Publisher”** ) on the website of www.ebolaplay.com ( **“Website”** ) operated by E-BOLA MÉDIA Kft. ( **”Ebola”** ).

This Privacy Policy informs you of what data is collected by Ebola, for what purposes and how that data is used and also how you can protect your personal data.

### A.) THE USE OF DATA PROVIDED BY THE PUBLISHERS

## What data should be given by the registered Publishers?

In order to use the services, the Publishers have to sign up on the Website. For registration, the following details must be given:

  * full name, e-mail address, telephone number, password;
  * payment related financial details (domicile or place of residence; tax number; mother’s name, “TAJ” (i.e. the Hungarian social security number), place and date of birth; bank account number, IBAN, SWIFT code);
  * other details that are given by the Publisher to Ebola in order to publish specified contents in connection with the Ebola Play on its own website;
  * content of the communication and contact with the Publisher;
  * answers given by the Publisher in the course of any market research.

## Who has access to the Publisher’s data?

Personal data given by the Publisher is processed by Ebola. The Publisher expressly gives its consent to such data processing in the last stage of the Website registration.

## For what purposes and for how long is the Publisher’s data managed?

Ebola uses the Publisher’s data for the following purposes:

  * communication with the primary purpose of providing the Publisher with appropriate information, efficient and rapid fixing of any technical problems and sending system messages relating to the service;
  * market research, answering questionnaires, consumer surveys;
  * sending direct marketing messages and advertising, if the Publisher expresses its relevant consent; in this case Ebola sends advertisement messages to the addresses given by the Publisher, or gets in touch with the Publisher by telephone for promoting its own products or services;
  * Ebola may regularly request that the Publishers publish certain campaigns on their websites via the Ebola Play.

Ebola processes the personal data until the management of such data has ceased to have any purpose. In principal, the personal data is only processed over the course of using Ebola’s services and during the period of the distribution.

## The Publishers’s rights relating to its data being processed

If so requested, Ebola can inform the Publisher about it’s personal data processed by Ebola, information about the purpose, the legal basis and the period of the data management and about its related activities can be provided. You may request information by sending an email to the email address [support@ebolaplay.com](mailto:support@ebolaplay.com). Ebola replies in writing no later than 30 (thirty) working days after the receipt of the request. The Publisher is entitled to request the correction of its personal data (by giving the correct data) by sending an email to the email address [support@ebolaplay.com](mailto:support@ebolaplay.com). Ebola carries out the correction in its records without delay and notifies the party concerned thereof in writing.

In addition to the above, the Publisher may ask, at any time, to delete, partly or wholly, its data, without needing to give reasons for this. This can be done by sending an email to the email address [support@ebolaplay.com](mailto:support@ebolaplay.com) or by post by sending a letter to the address 1026 Budapest, Riadó u. 7. After receiving the deletion request, Ebola stops the processing of the relevant data without delay, permanently deregisters the Publisher by making the identity of the party making the cancellation statement clear and notifies thereof. 

If such cancellation only concerns the direct marketing related data processing, Ebola will only delete the party concerned from the DM register without delay; otherwise Ebola shall remain entitled to process the Publisher’s data for providing services. 

For modifying or deleting the data, Ebola may request to provide a certificate for identifying the authorised person or may request that the Publisher requests the modification of the data via the email address made available in the registration. 

### B.) GENERAL RULES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED OTHERWISE IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THE WEBSITE

## What information is collected on the Website?

Ebola may collect data and information relating to the use of the Website when you visit the Website, right before you log in or after you have used the Website. Such data and information is generated over the course of using the Website and is recorded by Ebola’s system as an automatic result of technical processes. This information is transferred to Ebola via cookies, web beacons or similar devices. By using these devices, you do not need to give all login information at each login, since the relevant details are already stored in a cookie. When logging in, the browser automatically inserts these details into the appropriate boxes.

### C.) DATA SECURITY

Ebola takes all measures necessary to ensure that data is managed in a secure manner and protected against damage and has established and operates the systems of data management required thereto. Ebola ensures that no unauthorised persons can gain access to, make public, transfer, modify or delete any data being processed. All data being processed can only be accessed by the Ebola employees involved. Employees involved must not transfer such data to any unauthorised parties.

Ebola will use its best efforts to prevent data from accidental damage or destruction. Ebola also requires its employees involved in the data processing to meet the above obligations.

Under no circumstances does Ebola collect sensitive data, i.e. personal data revealing racial origin, affiliation to national and ethnic minority, political opinions or party affiliation, religious or other beliefs, membership in representation organisations, as well as personal data concerning health, pathological addiction or sexual life and criminal personal data. 

Publishers and Visitors who feel that their right to the protection of personal data has been violated may appeal to the competent authority for legal remedy, in accordance with the governing law.

**Data processing registration No.: NAIH-70646/2013.**

**Last update: 1st of November 2013**

**E-BOLA MÉDIA Kft.**
